A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Grants, Accession 2015:115 FA1321
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1979-2007; 1
  - National Asian Pacific American Legal Consortium - Exhibit 1-20 - 09801632, 2001-2003 (Box 23, Folder 156)
    Board of Directors information, The Reporter newsletters, surveys, flyers, fact sheets, and conference agendas
  - Center for Legal and Social Studies - 08600425, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 157)
    Copies of microfiche - form and correspondence
    - Center for Legal and Social Studies (C.E.L.S.) - Argentina Habeas Corpus Carcel Olmos - Microform, 1990 (Box 23, Item 2015:115:034)
  - Women's Inspiration Community (WICom) - STD/HIV/AIDS Education and Prevention Project for Military and Police Personnel in Nepal Progress Report, Nepal - 09900959, 1999 July 17-2000 July 16 (Box 23, Folder 158)
    Submitted to the Ford Foundation New Delhi
  - North Central Regional Center for Rural Development/Southern Rural Development Center - Year Three Report - Phase Two, Rural Community College Initiative (RCCI) - 09701832, 2005 June 30 (Box 24, Folder 159)
  - The Mountain Institute, Inc. - Purcellville, West Virginia - 10100732, 1998-2001 (Box 24, Folder 160)
    Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Office of Vice President (OVP)
    Includes: Sacred Mountains and Environmental Conservation: A Practitioner's Workshop, April 1998; Financial Statements and Supplemental Material 1998-1999; Senior People at the Mountain Institute 2001; Sacred Trees, Sacred Mountains: Pilgrimage and Conservation in the Himalaya, Edwin Bernbaum
  - New York Foundation for the Arts - Observatory of Cultural Policies in Africa (OCPA) - 10001348, 2006-2007 (Box 24, Folder 161-162)
    Includes: Compendum of Reference Documents for Cultural Policies in Africa Published in Co-operation with UNESCO and the Swiss Commission for UNESCO, Observatory of Cultural Policies in Africa (OCPA), Maputo, February 2006; Sexuality and Reproductive Health Learning Group (SRHLG) Update Volume 3 Issue 1, January 2006; LAFF Newsletter (Life After Ford Foundation) Summer 2008
  - Brooklyn Academy of Music (BAM) - 10000819, 1999-2001 (Box 24, Folder 163)
    Includes: A Report on Brooklyn Academy of Music's 2000 Next Wave Festival; Press Clippings
  - Brooklyn Academy of Music (BAM): Ford Foundation Grant, Meeting - 10000819, 2001 February 1 (Box 24, Folder 164)
    Sections include: 1. Proposal to Ford; 2. Ford Award Letter; 3. BAM Endowment Trust (BET) By-Laws; 4. Investment Guidelines; 5. Investment Results; 6. Segregated Account; 7. BET Board Meeting Minutes 5/25/00; 8. FY 2000 Audit; 9. Match Analysis; 10. Strategic Plan; 11. Cash Reserve Policy
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music (BAM) - 2000 Next Wave Festival photos, 2000 October (Box 24, Item 2015:115:035)
      Includes When Nights Were Dark and Tree: Part 2 of The Geography Trilogy
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music (BAM) - '99 Next Wave, BAM Cafe, and BAM's 20th Next Wave Festival slides, 1999 (Box 24, Item 2015:115:036)
  - Western Folklife Center - 10000793, 2000-2002; Digital media in folder - CD-R - Western Folklife Center, Ford Foundation - JPEG Image Files, 2001 March and - CD - Western Folklife Center - untitled, undated (Box 24, Folder 165)
    Fact Sheet, Photos of events
    - CD-R - Western Folklife Center, Ford Foundation - JPEG Image Files, 2001 March; CD-R (Box 24, Item 2015:115:037)
    - Western Folklife Center - Literature - slides, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Item 2015:115:038)
    - CD - untitled, undated; CD (Box 24, Folder 165)
  - CD - World Social Forum - Porto Alegre, Brazil - Reports to the Ford Foundation - 10300176, 2003 January 23-28; CD (Box 24, Item 2015:115:039)
  - International Labor Organization (ILO) - 10000619, 2002-2004 (Box 25, Folder 166-167)
    Folder 166: ILO and InFocus Programme on Boosting Employment through Small EnterpriseE Development (SEED) - Workshop Report: National Workshop on Small Enterprise Development and Job Creation in the Culture Sector; ILO and SEED - Workshop Report: Regional Workshop on SADC Regional Consultation and ILO Roundtable Discussion, Cape Town, South Africa, 11-13 October 2002; IFP-SEED Working Paper: Promoting Small Firms and Job Creation in the Cultural Industries of Southern Africa: A Summary of Five ILO Research Reports and Policy Recommendations, Geneva, 16 September 2003; Employment Generation and Trade Expansion in Creative Industries: the case of the film, video, and broadcast industry in Senegal, Prepared for ILO
    Folder 167: Report from the Workshop on "Boosting Job Creation through Promoting Cultural Tourism in Zambia" Organized by The Zambian Ministry of Tourism; Projet de Programme General; Start Your Cultural Activity As A Business Draft (SYCAB): A Step-by-Step Guide for Artists to Start Their Activities as a Business
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation (MDRC) - The Career Academies Evaluation: Impacts on High School Graduation Rates and Initial Transitions to Post-Secondary Education and Employment - 09800819, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 168)
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation (MDRC) - 09800819, 1988-2000 (Box 25, Folder 169-171)
    Folder 169: Considering the Major Arguments Against Random Assignment: An Analysis of the Intellectual Culture Surrounding Evaluation in American Schools of Education, Thomas D. Cook, Northwestern University, March 1999; Comer's School Development Program in Chicago: A Theory-Based Evaluation, Thomas D. Cook, H. David Hunt, Robert F. Murphy, Northwestern University; Using Cluster Random Assignment to Measure Program Impacts: Statistical Implications for the Evaluation of Education Programs, Howard S. Bloom, Johannes M. Bos, Suk-Won Lee, April 1988; Career Academies: Building Connections Between School and Work, James J. Kemple, Susan M. Poglinco, Jason Snipes
    Folder 170: Project Transition Report; Media Coverage of Career Academies Impacts on Students' Engagement and Performance in High School (Released February 2000)
    Folder 171: Selected MDRC Press Clippings 1998
  - Haitian Refugee Center, Inc. - Master Exhibit on Human Rights Violations, Repression, and the Persecution of Returnees in Haiti - 08200952, 1983 October 1 (Box 26, Folder 172)
  - Pacific Community Ventures - Emerging Enterprises Business Advising - 10150652, 2004 December (Box 26, Folder 173)
  - Morehouse School of Medicine - Parent Training Network Development Program - State Capitol Day, Georgia State Capitol Building - Photo Album - 09600958, 1997 February 24 (Box 26, Item 2015:115:040)
  - American Youth Policy Forum - Attachment A-C - 09801761, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 174)
    Includes: Activities 1998-1999; Descriptions of Seminars regarding At-Risk Youth; Forum Trip Reports: Baltimore, MD and Detroit, MI; American Youth Policy Forum 1998; Site Visit to Bergen County Technical Schools Career Academies; Contact Information
  - The Fatherhood Project - Final Report Submitted to Ford Foundation Southern Africa - Linda Richter - 10351404, 2004 September 6 (Box 26, Folder 175)
  - Houston Grand Opera - Cold Sassy Tree and Little Women photos - 10000817, undated (Box 26, Item 2015:115:041)
  - Houston Grand Opera - slides, 1995-2000 (Box 26, Item 2015:115:042)
    Includes slides of Little Women and La Cenerentola
  - Clark Atlanta University - Correspondence - 10100603, 2003 May 13 (Box 26, Folder 176)
    One piece of correspondence regarding submission of financial materials
  - Redess Jovenes: Red Nacional de Educacion Salud Sexual Desarolilo Para Loveness - Taller: Violencia y Abuso Sexual en Jovenes - 09550822, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 177)
  - Program in Labor Economics - Programa de Economia Del Trabajo (PET) - 10150998, 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 178)
    Includes: Anexo Copias de Convenios de Colaboracion, Santiago; Informe Final Estudio de Factibilidad Fundacion Contigo, December 2002
  - Program in Labor Economics - Programa de Economia Del Trabajo (PET) - 10150998, 2003; Digital media in folder - CD - Con Esfuerzo Y Creatividad Contamos Con Tu Apoyo, Con el Financiamiento de la Fundacion Ford, 2006 April 26 (Box 27, Folder 179)
    Informe de Actividades, Enero-May de 2003: Nombre del Proyecto: Continuidad y Consolidacion del Estudio Microempresa Informalidad y Credito-Generacion de un Centro Intregal de Estudio, Asesoria y Capacitacion Para el Financiamiento a la Microempresa/Fundacion Ford, Jose Andres Herrera Chavaia
    Diplomado En Microfinanzas y Credito para Microempresas: Estudio de Oferta, Demanda, Factibilidad y Programa de Estudios, Universidad Bolivariana
    - CD - Con Esfuerzo Y Creatividad Contamos Con Tu Apoyo, Con el Financiamiento de la Fundacion Ford, 2006 April 26; CD (Box 27, Item 2015:115:043)
  - Casa Via Magia - IV Mercado Cultural: Pesquisa de Impacto Economico e Estrategico - 09900720, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 180)
  - Casa Via Magia - IV Mercado Cultural - Clipping 1-3 - 09900720, 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 181-182, Box 28, Folder 183)
  - Centro de Desenvolvimento de Capacidades, undated (Box 45, Folder 328)
    Special format items have been separated from the body of the collection and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
  - Northwest Normal University - Improving Development of Basic Education in the Poor and Minority Nationalities - Inhabited Regions in Gansu Province, Final Report - 10051960, 2004 October (Box 28, Folder 184)
    Improving Access to Education for Girls and Minorities in Poor Regions - $94,000 - Field Office File
  - International Reading Association, Inc. - Asociacion Internacional de Lectura - Informe Annual, Asociacion Panamena de Lectura - 10100668, 2002 October 15 (Box 28, Folder 185)
    Reunion del Comite Latinoamericano para el Desarrollo de la Lectura y la Escritura, Puebla, Republica de Mexico
  - Washington University - Center for Social Development - The Potential for Inclusion in 529 Savings Plans: Report on a Survey of States, Margaret Clancy and Michael Sherradan - 10201362, 2003 December (Box 28, Folder 186)
  - Instituto para Artes Escenicas Digitales - 10351770, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 187)
    Cuestionario del talleres - Seminarios en Guadalajara
    Dossier de Prensa: Mexican Performing Artists and Organizations, New York, Mexico Gateway to the Arts, January 21 to 24, 2006
  - Chinese Women's College - The Indigenization of Women's Studies Teaching - Asian Experiences - 10251770, 2002 October 19-21 (Box 28, Folder 188)
  - Independent Television Service (ITVS) - INPUT 2005 - The International Public Television Conference, September 2004 Status Report, San Francisco - 10450374, 2005 May 1-6 (Box 28, Folder 189)
    Knowledge Creativity and Freedom (KCF)/Media Arts and Culture (MAC)
  - The Synergos Institute - Proposal to the Ford Foundation and Proposal Appendices - 10001576, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 190)
  - Swaminathan Research Foundation - 09901353, 1997-2000 (Box 28, Folder 191)
    Includes correspondence, Biovillages: Pathway to Human Centered Rural Development, Inauguration of the GOI-UNDP, Biocentre, Pillayarkuppan Village, Pondicherry, India; Information and Communication Technologies for the Empowerment of the Rural Families; Resource Centre in Gender and Development; Essay - Sustainable Development - Five Years after Rio, Dr. M. S. Swaminathan, Chairman, MSSRF, February 1997
  - Aspen Institute, Inc. - Global Interdependence Initiative - Proposal - 09901561, 2000-2002 (Box 28, Folder 192)
    Tabs A and B
  - Aspen Institute, Inc. - Global Interdependence Initiative Working Group Context, Memos, and February 2001 Meeting - 09901561 (Box 28, Folder 193)
    Tab 1. Agenda; Tab 2. The Mind and the World: Changing the Very Idea of American Foreign Policy (Edited Excerpts), George Lakoff; Tab 3. A Window on the Storm: How TV Global News Promotes a Cognitive "Refuge Stance;" Tab 4. Contribution to Panel Discussion on Globalization and Education Meeting of the Board of Trustees of the American Forum for Global Education, Priscilla Lewis; Tab 5. Youth Activism and Global Engagement: Charting the Field (Summary), Benton Foundation; Tab 6. Memo: Indicators; Tab 7. America's Unipolarity Problem, G. John Ikenberry; Tab 8. Contact Information
  - Aspen Institute, Inc. - Talking Global Interdependence: A Framework Toolkit for the Global Interdependence Initiative - 09901561, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 194-195)
    Folder 194: About This Toolkit; Strategic Frame Analysis; Elements of the Frame; Framing Global Interdependence
    Folder 195: Exemplary Materials; Framing Tactics; Framing for Access and Content; Additional Resources
  - Aspen Institute, Inc. - Interdependence Initiative - Office Files - 09901561, 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 196)
    Introduction - Phase 2 Research; 10 Differences Between Public and Expert Understandings of International Affairs: Findings from the Mainstream American Press, Joseph Grady, Axel Aubrun; Metaphorical Thought in Foreign Policy: Why Strategic Framing Matters, George Lakoff; Four Habits of International News Reporting, Susan Moeller; Veterans of Perception: GII Antecedents in the Literature on Media and Foreign Policy, Susan Nall Bales; Communications and Foreign Policy: A Brief Annotated Bibliography of the Recent Literature, Susan Nall Bales, Adria Goodson
  - Aspen Institute, Inc. - Global Interdependence Initiative Planning Meeting, Wye River Conference Centers, Queenstown, MD - 09901561, 1999 May 26-27 (Box 29, Folder 197)
  - Aspen Institute, Inc. - Global Interdependence Initiative (GII) Working Group Meeting, Pocantico Conference Center, Tarrytown, New York - 09901561, 2000 July 31-August 2 (Box 29, Folder 198)
  - National Fair Housing Alliance (NHFA) - "Safe and Sound" - Anti-Predatory Lending Campaign - 10251767, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 199)
    Assets/(Economic Development)ED
  - Arias Foundation for Peace and Human Progress - Central American Dialogue for Security and Demilitarization, Phase Three - 09800460, 1998-2001 (Box 30, Folder 200)
    Includes: Correspondence; Central American Dialogue for Security and Demilitarization Phase Three: Narrative Report on the Project's Progress; Project: "Central American Dialogue for Security and Demilitarization" 2001 Financial Report, San Jose, Costa Rica; Annual Report 2001; Financial Report as of December 31, 1998
  - University of Khartoum - An Explanatory Text for the Map of the Environmental Context of Development in Sudan - 09500260, 1982 May (Box 30, Folder 201)
  - Corporation for Enterprise Development - Evaluation of the American Dream Demonstration (ADD): Semi-Annual Progress Report - July-December 2000 - 09701062, 2001 February 12 (Box 30, Folder 202)
  - Corporation for Enterprise Development - Center for Social Development - Washington University in St. Louis - Progress of the American Dream Demonstration (ADD) Evaluation - 09701062, 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 203)
  - The Discrimination Research Center - 10201369, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 204)
    Racial Preferences: The Treatment of White and African American Job Applicants by Temporary Employment Agencies in California by Jenny Bussey and John Trasvina of the Discrimination Research Center, a program of The Impact Fund, December 2003
    Proposition 209 and the Decline of Women in the Construction Trades, Produced by The Discrimination Research Center and Equal Rights Advocates, June 2004
  - Oregon Public Broadcasting (OPB) - Rocks with Wings - 09701097, 2002-2005 (Box 30, Folder 205)
    Report with budget information, general information, and press material
  - Urban Institute - 09801362, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 206)
    Notes; Urban Institute Agenda; Low-Income Adults without Children: Characteristics, Work Patterns, and Public Support, Stephen Bell and L. Jerome Gallagher; Publications and Products of Assessing the New Federalism - Occasional Papers; Preliminary Findings from the National Survey of America's Families on Child Support Related Issues; Discussion Paper 99-02 - Families Who Left Welfare: Who Are They and How Are They Doing?: Dissemination Strategy and Progress Report
  - Academy for the Development of Philanthropy, Poland - The Dialogue of Cultures Programme - 10251174, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 207)
    Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC)/Governance and Civil Society (GCS)
  - Spelman College - 10301076 - Giving Voice: Protecting, Preserving, Validating Traditional Knowledge Throughout the Global Community - Progress Report Year One, 2003 April 1-2005 March 31; CDs (Box 30)
  - Spelman College - 10301076 - Giving Voice: Protecting, Preserving, Validating Traditional Knowledge Throughout the Global Community - Progress Report Year Two, 2003 April 1-2005 March 31; CD (Box 30)
  - Royal Tropical Institute - Gender, Citizenship and Governance in South Asia and Southern Africa - 09900874, 2001-2002 (Box 30, Folder 208)
    Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Governance and Civil Society (GCS)/OSP
    Narrative Report, Action Research, Project Proposals, South Asian Region and Southern Africa Region
  - Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development - Winrock International India - Proposal - Small Grants Management in Natural Resources Management - 09900975, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 209)
  - Ateneo de Davao University - Ateneo Task Force and Mindanao Working Group On Reproductive Health, Gender, and Sexuality - Gender Sensitivity Training for Private School Administrators - 09600995, 2002 May 8-10 (Box 31, Folder 210)
  - Ateneo de Davao University - Ateneo Task Force and Mindanao Working Group On Reproductive Health, Gender, and Sexuality - Re-Echo Trainings and Conferences - 09600995, 2000 August 4 (Box 31, Folder 211)
  - Ateneo de Davao University - Mindanao Working Group On Reproductive Health, Gender, and Sexuality - Gender Sensitivity Training with Media Practitioners - 09600995, 2002 January 25-27 (Box 31, Folder 212)
  - Ateneo de Davao University - Ateneo Task Force and Mindanao Working Group On Reproductive Health, Gender, and Sexuality - Gender Sensitivity Training for Government Executives - 09600995, 2004 May 22-24 (Box 31, Folder 213)
  - Ateneo de Davao University - Ateneo Task Force and Mindanao Working Group On Reproductive Health, Gender, and Sexuality - Forum on Human Rights Education: Women's Rights as Human Rights - 09600995, 2002 February 8-9 (Box 31, Folder 214)
  - Ateneo de Davao University - Ateneo Task Force and Mindanao Working Group On Reproductive Health, Gender, and Sexuality - Communicating Population and Health Research to Policy Makers - 09600995, 2001 May 21-23 (Box 31, Folder 215)
  - Ateneo de Davao University - Ateneo Task Force and Mindanao Working Group On Reproductive Health, Gender, and Sexuality - Legislative Advocacy Training - 09600995, 2001 April 19-21 (Box 31, Folder 216)
  - Ateneo de Davao University - Ateneo Task Force and Mindanao Working Group On Reproductive Health, Gender, and Sexuality - Indigenous People's Beliefs and Coping Practices in Reproductive Health - 09600995, 2001 October (Box 31, Folder 217)
  - Ateneo de Davao University - Ateneo Task Force and Mindanao Working Group On Reproductive Health, Gender, and Sexuality - Module Writers Meeting - 09600995, 2002 April 1-3 (Box 31, Folder 218)
  - The Finance Project - Collaborative Initiative on Financing Professional Development in Education, Washington, D. C. - 10000959, 2003 March 20 (Box 31, Folder 219)
  - The Finance Project - Collaborative Initiative on Financing Professional Development in Education Advisory Group Meeting - 10000959, 2003 October 30 (Box 32, Folder 220)
  - The Finance Project - Improving Educational Achievement: A Forum Exploring the Role of Investments in Schools and Other Supports and Services for Families and Communities - 10000959, 2000 September 15 (Box 32, Folder 221)
    Sponsored by The Finance Project and Center on Education Policy; Includes Agenda, Press Release, Biographical Summaries of Sponsors, and Contact List
  - Sixth International Conference on Thai Studies - 09651190, 1996 October 14-17 (Box 32, Folder 222)
    One piece of correspondence referring to a CD-ROM of contributed conference papers
  - CD-R - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management - 10350462 - Fish Fights over Fish Rights: Managing Exit From the Fisheries and Security Implications for Southeast Asia - Final Technical Report, 2005 August; CD-R (Box 32, Item 2015:115:047)
    By WorldFish Center - In collaboration with research partners: University of the Philippines in the Visayas, Department of Fisheries - Cambodia, Southern Marine Fisheries Development Centre and Coastal Resources Institute - Thailand, and the University of Cape Town, South Africa
  - Smithsonian National Museum of the American Indian (NMAI) - Final Narrative Report: Video Mexico Indigena/Video Native Mexico - Attachments - 10351159, 2005 February (Box 32, Folder 223)
    Knowledge Creativity and Freedom (KCF)/Media Arts and Culture (MAC)/OVS
  - New Jersey Performing Arts Center (NJPAC) - FY2003 Endowment Report and Artistic Programming Update - 10000822, 2001-2003 (Box 32, Folder 224)
    - New Jersey Performing Arts Center (NJPAC) 1999/2000 Season - National Song and Dance Company of Mozambique - 2 Slides (Box 32, Item 2015:115:048)
  - The Institute for Educational Leadership, Inc. - Leadership for Student Learning: Recognizing the State's Role in Public Education - Press Release and Article - 10000177, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 225)
    Note on original folder: In Storage Reel No. 9089
  - Peoples' Science Institute (PSI) - Jal Sanskriti: From Consumption to Conservancy - Survival Lessons - Progress Report - 10050476, 2002-2004 (Box 32, Folder 226)
  - Peoples' Science Institute (PSI) - Annexure I: Survival Lessons: Water Management Traditions in the Central-Western Himalayas - 10050476, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 227)
  - Manchester Craftsmen's Guild - Martin Luther King, Jr. Photographic Exhibition, Countdown to Eternity, Benedict J. Fernandez - Slides - 09300481, undated (Box 32, Item 2015:115:049)
  - Urgent Action Fund: For Women's Human Rights - Africa - Final Report to the Ford Foundation's Trust Africa - 10300356, 2003-2005 (Box 32, Folder 228)
    Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Office of Vice President (OVP)
  - Madras Craft Foundation - Annual Report Submitted to the Ford Foundation - 09100832, 1993 April 1-1994 March 31 (Box 32, Item 2015:115:050)
    Developing Country Programs (DCP)/Education and Culture (EC)
    Photographs adhered to report's pages
  - Madras Craft Foundation - Annual Report for the Ford Foundation - 09100832, 1992 April 1-1993 March 30 (Box 32, Item 2015:115:051)
    Photos adhered to report
  - Madras Craft Foundation - Annual Report to the Ford Foundation - 09100832, 2000 April 1-2001 March 31 (Box 32, Item 2015:115:052)
    Photos adhered to pages of report
  - Madras Craft Foundation - Annual Report to the Ford Foundation - 09100832, 1997 April 1-1998 March 31 (Box 32, Item 2015:115:053)
    Photos attached to report
  - Madras Craft Foundation - Annual Report to the Ford Foundation - 09100832, 1994 April 1-1995 March 31 (Box 32, Item 2015:115:054)
    Includes photographs adhered to pages of the report
  - Madras Craft Foundation - DakshinaChitra - Your Community Heritage Center - Brochures and Photographs from Performances - 09100832, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Item 2015:115:055)
  - Roja Productions - Matters of Race - 10301835, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 229, Box 33, Folder 230)
    Educators' guides, reviews, website feedback examples, press examples, PBS public program guide examples, screenings
  - Ateneo de Davao University - Gender Sensitivity Training for the Cotabato Public Secondary School Administrators Association - 09600995, 2001 May 29-31 (Box 33, Folder 231)
    Ateneo Task Force and Mindanao Working Group on Reproductive Health, Gender and Sexuality